Please contact turkision@gmail.com
for any inquiries
NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING
THE FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION.
If let that rebel escape,
the Emperor will hang us all!
We'll scatter.
Go this way
You're now in my lands.
I'll send your heads to the Emperor.
My Alaca.
We have lots of secrets.
Do you want us to tell one
to Osman Bey?
Karayel! Do you hear what
Alaca and Bala Hatun are saying?
They have secrets.
What could they be?
We say...
We run as fast as...
... our hearts fly with love.
Who loves the most,
runs the fastest.
Karayel!
Did you hear that?
Look what they're saying to us.
But they don't know that for love...
... we'll fly like the wind in
the whole world.
Then show us, Osman Bey.
Karayel...
Come on.
It's time to fly like the wind.
Osman?
Sofia is here!
I'll take a thousand of your lives for
every breath you stole from Master Yannis.
Neither you...
... nor those damn Turks will
be able to stop me.
You must be hungry.
You've come from a long trip.
I'll fill you up.
How nice of you to come here.
Aygül.
Aygül!
Mother, look!
Look, Batur brother is here!
He wants pancakes.
Let's eat together.
My Aygül...
My beautiful daughter...
Your brother Batur won't come.
Don't do this.
Your brother won't come back.
He met his maker.
He's in heaven now.
Look! He's here.
He wants pancakes.
My brother came to me.
Pull yourself together, child.
Your brother is dead.
Let's go to his grave
and pray, my daughter.
Enough! You think he is dead
because you killed him!
I didn't kill my brother!
That's why he ignores you and comes to me!
Brother?
My brother is gone.
He's gone.
My Aygül...
... don't do this, my daughter.
Come, my daughter. Come on.
Come on, my daughter.
Come.
My brother is gone because of you!
Because of you!
Look.
They're beating me up, brother.
Same me from them, Batur brother.
Save me.
Come on.
Help yourself.
You must be thirsty.
We couldn't beat each other, huh?
Don't I know you, Osman?
If you wanted to win, I couldn't catch
you on top of an eagle.
My heart shakes this way
for this first time, Osman.
I'm very happy!
Your heart is strong. Both your faith
and creed are like steel, my Bala.
But happiness is a test
just like pain.
That's why your heart shakes.
We'll get through these tests together.
The banners we put on
the enemy's lands...
... will be carried
father by our children.
I'll be with you
as far as I can go, Osman.
I don't know if I can give you a child.
But the only thing I know is
that I'll sacrifice my life to your cause.
My Allah knows the best.
May my Allah keep you with me.
It will happen if we belive it.
I'm not saying that with my mind...
... but with my heart.
We'll have children.
Our lineage will keep going.
Hopefully, Osman.
Hopefully.
May my Allah allow us to be victorious.
May Allah allow us to be from
those who always believe...
... do good deeds and warn each
other to be patient and kind.
Amen.
The day will come and children
noises will be all over our tents!
That day, the mighty state of the united
Turkish Tents will be established.
The name of the rule
of justice and freedom...
... will be heard from far away.
With Hatuns raised by Bala Hatun,
and Osman Bey's soldiers...
... we'll fly our banners everywhere!
With Allah's help, we'll
see those days, my Bala.
Hopefully, Osman.
Come on!
Why are we staying here like this?
You asked for a race.
Bring it on!
-The first one to arrive at the Tent wins.
-Let's do it!
- Let's go!
They got married hastily.
They've sacrificed lots, and lots,
and lots of animals.
Lots of animals.
They wasted a young bride.
Look! We picked these
flowers with my brother Batur.
I'll put them to our brides head
during the wedding.
Do they look nice on me, father?
What wouldn't look good on an angel,
my daughter?
I'll decorate everywhere with
such flowers once I'm a bride.
We will, my daughter.
My Bey.
What will we do about our daughter?
Shall we find a famous bogyman,
or a talented healer?
We need a remedy.
Gündüz said we should find a good healer.
He is sending criers to every part
of Söğüt.
Inshallah, we'll find
a good doctor, Hatun.
Inshallah, my Bey.
Inshallah.
My Bey...
You haven't eaten anything for days.
I'll bring you food.
I'm in no mood to eat.
You know my daughter's condition...
...and Bahadır...
...is being watched in his own home.
If Hazal Hatun had come here...
...and ask me ''What is my son's
situation?''...
...what could I say to her?
Now...
...is the time you are needed
the most...
...I'll bring it anyways.
- Welcome. Welcome.
Thank you, thank you.
Kayı Tent has grown up a lot since
the last time.
It became the largest one in the area.
After all, it has everything needed.
- Gold and battles.
- Politics, Saltukay.
Science of Politics.
Without it, neither the gold nor
the weapon have any value.
When we enter the Tent,
many will come to my door.
Know that I don't want tactless people
at my door.
As you wish, Hazal Hatun.
Don't worry.
Hazal...
Subutay who brings bad luck
to wherever he goes.
One who doesn't make a hundred
dogs bark after...
...cannot be called a wolf.
Now stop howling with your
foam at your mouth...
...which is filled with decayed
tooth...
...and take me to Balgay.
- How did you find our track?
-We fought many battles with Balgay.
I can smell his blood from miles away.
Take me to Balgay. I have
important things to say to him.
I would die here rather than betraying
Balgay, don't you know that?
If you don't take me to Balgay...
...then, you will be betraying him.
And is Balgay the Merciless incapable
of handling my three warriors?
Don't you see it? It's only me and my
three warriors.
When it's time to do your
own job...
...a man wears his boots and
gets on his way.
I wore my boots and came here.
Cerkutay, Balgay will be glad
to see me...
...after all the times I protected
him in battles.
Come on now. Take me to Balgay.
Hazal Hatun...
Dündar Bey.
Welcome, Hatun.
Thank you.
You are spreading joy, Zöhre.
Won't you welcome me?
Welcome.
With your one word,
I came as swift as the wind.
Firstly, my condolences...
...I heard about what happened.
Thank you, Hatun.
Thank you.
Sit.
I sent Saltuk Alp to you.
But if you had told me that you were
close, I would send another Alp to greet you.
It isn't safe, Hatun.
I'm the wife of the most renowned
Bey of Bithynia...
...and sister of strongest Bey of Nikea.
What can happen to us, Dündar Bey?
- Welcome, Hazal Hatun.
- Thank you, Gündüz. May you live long.
- Mother.
- Your mother loves you.
My valiant without fear.
Gündüz! Strong Gündüz.
The position of Bey fits you well.
Thank you, thank you.
My brother, Bey of Çobanoğulları
greets you.
Because that Kayıs are jihadists...
...he sent ulufe(service pay) to help you.
We greet him as well.
But Kayıs don't jihad with ulufe...
...but with faith.
No doubt on that, valiant.
We gave it with nobleness...
...and you refused it with your
blue blood.
As you wish.
- Welcome, Hazal Hatun.
- Thank you, Selcan Hatun.
You are welcome indeed.
But what is the purpose of
your visit?
Did your longing for Dündar Bey
break the ice?
Longing is the friend of those
who love, Selcan Hatun.
Of course, I missed...
...my tent, kins...
...and my husband.
But let's not call it a visitation...
...but residation for a while.
Well, well...
Good.
Thank God.
Jesus Christ saved you.
We heard what happened to Efendi Yannis.
We are deeply sad.
Emperor's soldiers are after me.
They won't stop until they take me.
If you want, we can go to Nikea for
a while.
We still have loyal friends in there.
No, Helen. There are men waiting to take
my life as soon as I leave the castle.
And I can't trust anyone.
Soldiers, to your posts.
I'll take every precaution.
If you wish, we can dig bulwarks
and get to the war position.
You know that won't be enough to
beat the Emperor's army.
But, for salvation...
...we have one chance.
- We'll do anything.
The only power that can protect us from
the Emperor...
...is Kayı Tent.
Salvador, you will go there...
....and tell them that...
...I agree with all the terms they want
to be allies. Even tribute...
Osman Bey will never accept that...
...we have no other chance than
making him accept it.
The fate of my people and my own
is on your hands.
I give you unlimited authorization.
Tell Osman that I accept all the terms.
Yes, Princess.
Mashallah. Renown of Kayı Tent
reaches to Nikea.
Especially Osman...
...his battles became songs
for the youth.
I didn't see him. Where is he?
You must've heard it. We'll have
the wedding meeting.
They are on a hurry with Bala Hatun.
He'll be here soon.
Well, this is the order of this world...
...wedding on the one side and
mourning on the other.
One side is birth and the other
side is death.
You said ''Osman'' and now he is coming.
Mashallah. They match each other.
Mashallah.
It has been a while.
Welcome.
I can't see you by the light
of our bride, Osman.
May I?
Mashallah. May Allah protect her from
evil eyes...
...she shines like the sun.
Now...
...you say that, why did this
Hazal Hatun...
...return to the Tent?
After all, this time, which wind
brought her here?
Know that it isn't a wind...
...but a fire.
The fire of a mother in my heart.
You are keeping my Bahadır under
open arrest.
And you forbid him to leave the
Tent.
Then...
...you know what happened, Hazal Hatun.
Messengers at borders are more agile
than your weapon, Bamsı Bey.
Is there anyone who hasn't heard yet?
We all know what this dog Alişar did.
We are informed.
But my brother doesn't want the
blood of a brother...
...to be spilled for the sins of Alişar.
Why did you do that?
It won't be long before Osman hear
I'm here.
And as soon as he hears it, he will come
here with his alps.
Then why did we send word?
Geyhatu's arrival at Söğüt is a
matter of time.
Until he does, we need to gain time.
And the enemy within, Salvador...
...will gain that time.
You brought us joy with your
arrival at Dündar Bey's mournful tent.
But you should know, Hazal Hatun...
This well is too deep. To see the truth...
...you should see its bottom.
Selcan Hatun...
...blue-eyed Selcan Hatun...
...thank Allah, there is no well too deep
for us to not see its bottom.
There is no need to blur the point
with fancy words, aunt.
Bahadır moved against the Laws.
A post holds a tent, a Bey holds
the Tent...
...and justice holds the Law.
My Bahadır had blindness...
...but he isn't a traitor.
That matter is over, aunt.
The decision about him...
...will be made by our Bey when he
returns to the Tent.
Be at ease.
I have no doubt.
But Bahadır's uncles won't accept
any decision...
...the will result in Bahadır's death.
Aunt...
...like you are stuck between
motherhood and the Law...
...don't stick us between our
respect for you...
...and justice.
Çobanoğulları aren't like any other...
...Tents or Beys, my nephew.
If Çobanoğulları decides to intervere...
... the only thing I'm afraid is being
stuck in the middle.
I don't want to offend you or break
your heart...
I know the fire in your heart.
But, you should know...
...squares of Kayı Tent...
...is filled with heads of those
who tried to intervene.
We know you as a traditional person.
We love you because you are
a traditional person.
Don't be overwhelmed by your
feelings...
...so that your don't lose your dignity
against us.
Now, it's not the time to talk
these.
I have feast this evening.
You're all invited.
Now, take care.
We need to do preparation
for the feast.
You fulfill your longings.
Come on.
Did Geyhatu send you as ambassador?
Did you think...
...Osman who you trust would save you
from the fury of Geyhatu?
Osman needs me in order to be alive.
Balgay trusts someone else.
Geyhatu knows well what he wants
to do.
He took his precaution and came.
What kind of precaution?
I killed all the soldiers
one by one...
...who would fight with you and
I came here.
Now, you're alone, Balgay.
Shhhh!
You're still precious for Geyhatu,
Balgay.
The problem of Geyhatu is
Osman.
He wants him.
You know well that he will smash all
Kayı's and all Tents belong to them.
Sofia couldn't do the job.
If you give us Osman, by entering into Geyhatu's service
we can have the power to loot the Byzantium.
Did Geyhatu tell you that?
Either me or Geyhatu..
What difference does it make?
Do you think Geyhatu will want what
I don't want?
The grandson of Kulagu, Baytuğ wants
Geyhatu to be killed.
By conquering the Anatolia.
You...
You want to use my power to make
Geyhatu stronger.
You want to be exalted in Geyhatu's mind.
Balgay.
Come.
Come. Let's be strong together.
Let's be stronger and wealthier in the
uplands glorious as Tengri Mountain.
If you enter into Geyhatu's service...
...we'll be the winner.
When you're done, whom of you will behead
me?
I can save you from the fury of Geyhatu.
I can take your old dignity and
wealth back.
Your old soldier, your blood brother,
Subutay!
Princess Sofia.
From the Margaret monks, Alexis.
It's very nice to see you.
We heard about what happened to Mr. Yannis
and other monks.
Our all plans are failed because of a
goatherd named Osman.
We'll take our revenge together, Alexis.
I heard that the daughter of Dündar Bey got
sick and that they're looking for a doctor.
If you ask me to come for this,
you know I'm not a doctor.
I don't need a doctor. I need a magician...
...who can trick them with his plans.
In this pouch, we have the potion of our
revenge.
This potion will make you an
unforgettable hero, Alexis.
Now, listen to what I say carefully,
Alexis.
Uncle.
Zöhre Hatun.
And now, Hazal Hatun.
Hazal is not like Zöhre, my son.
She is powerful and knows
what to do in any condition.
I assume she won't adapt to
Zöhre.
That's the point, mother.
She is both powerful and respectful.
She can do unexpected move in an
unexpected time and you will be surprised.
You be careful, mother.
You know Zöhre Hatun. She's done
something like betrayal.
She never gets well with Hazal Hatun.
Hazal Hatun looks dignified.
Yes, she is.
The essence of man
is inside, my daughter.
Yes, it's inside.
Do you think why she came here
after years?
Just for Bahadır?
I don't think so.
As she is trying to threat us secretly...
...there is absolutely a problem.
You're right, my son.
You don't worry. I'll keep an eye on her.
With the fuss of the feast, we're
absent-minded.
Be careful about Hazal Hatun.
Those like her loves foggy weather.
Keep your eyes open.
What do you want, Zöhre Hatun?
Come and sit down you're standing
on your leg.
I didn't come here to have fun.
I have 2 words to tell you.
I hope nothing is wrong.
What's the reason
for your anger?
You came here for Dündar.
You're saying I'll stay
here for a short time.
But I know. You won't go until you
disturb my peace.
Dündar bey is engaged with me.
If he says don't go, I'll stay surely.
As for you, you'll get used to 3
mattresses in front of the Tent.
What can we do?
You.
Me.
And Dündar Bey.
I've relieved him for years after you.
He has relieved his pain
with my compassion.
I attached his sword to his waist
when he was going to the war.
So, why are you worrying then?
You've always scorned and looked down on
me.
You've looked down upon.
But it's over now.
You, Hazal Hatun, are coming from
a huge and noble Bey family.
I am an orphan from Karabudu, Zöhre.
You remember your place.
It's nice.
Then you must know how to speak
with me, Zöhre Hatun.
Be respectful and be yourself!
You speak right.
I'll remember
my place.
I'll not allow you.
It's not the old Zöhre against you.
You know this as well.
Go and pray.
Pray so that I don't get angry.
Who was the person that made Bahadır
and Dündar Bey offend to each other...
...and made us to leave from here with
my son?
Who was the person that
disturbed my peace?
Look, hatun.
I didn't come here by wishing revenge.
If my aim was to take revenge...
...you would have come back
to the Karabudu already.
My only worry is my son.
Now, go and mind your business!
Don't you ever do anything that will
make me angry!
If you do, you will witness my fury that
you haven't seen till now.
Only Allah knows who will witness
the fury of the other.
Know that Zöhre isn't the old
Zöhre.
Keep your eyes on her.
If she leaves the Tent...
If she meets with someone or speaks,
let me know.
Allright, Hazal Hatun.
The fruit of betrayal is sweet.
But it is also toxic.
Kongar...
Let's start with how you took him from slave
bazaar and made him a senseless slave.
Why do you have a treaty that you had made
a long time ago with...
...a slave merchant?
What kind of power is this?
Cerkutay.
Take soldiers and go with Boran.
Bring the laws to me.
If you let me, I'll take this dog,
commander Balgay.
If they do anything again,
I want to punish them.
Only aim in the war is to win.
It seems I didn't teach it to you well.
There surely will be price for
betrayal of Osman.
Commander Balgay.
Avoid from your poison.
Why were you so late? Where have you been?
After I rescued you, I followed Dündar
in order to ambush him.
But Osman acted before me
So, I came back.
I owe you my life, Kongar.
Wish what you want from me.
Revenge. I wish revenge,
commander Balgay.
I want to come with you to kill all
those who...
...revolt against you.
Betrayal to Balgay.
Betrayal to Osman is the victory.
Betrayal to Balgay is death
with the shame.
Cerkutay. Go up to Osman right now.
Tell him that we have new soldiers and
we are ready to fight with Geyhatu.
When he is cheering up, stab your
sword to his belly.
The poison of betrayal may flow
like a honey from your sword.
Osman will be the best present
for Erlik Han.
Go up to Osman, Cerkutay.
Boran.
Tonight, I'll hit my sword in such a power
to the shield that...
...its sound will be heard
from Kesis Mountain.
How magnificent, my brother.
It'll be heard...
But let's look who will be the best
in carrying sheeps.
The answer of your question
is that...
...when there is Konur Alp,
you are the you're the second.
Konur, Konur.
You're flying with your wings.
Don't fly too high.
You'll crash hard later.
You mind your business, Boran.
We'll see now who'll fly and who'll
crash to the ground.
You are witness, brother Dumrul.
If I defeat him, he'll walk around the
Tent with one leg like a gazelle.
Are you a witness?
Yes, brother.
Are you okay with that Konur?
Yes.
But I have a condition.
If you lose, you'll do the same.
That's okay, brother.
Dumrul. Listen what he say carefully...
...so that he don't object to it.
Come on.
Wonderful!
I'm a witness of you too, brother.
He's saying he'll fly, huh!
The wedding feast of Aybars was left half
finished.
But know I can see you're growing
up and get married.
From now on, I won't have sorrow
even if I die, my Osman.
Aybars brother will complete his wedding
in the paradise, Bamsi Bey.
May Allah allow us such a thing.
Amen.
Amen, son.
Allah took one of your son
and gave you another son, Bamsi brother.
He is such a boy that he is like a
lion. Praise be!
Thank you, Abdurrahman Gazi.
Welcome, my bey.
Sıddık.
Do you have any wish, my bey?
- Assalamu Alaikum
- Alaikum selam.
- Welcome.
- Thank you.
Thank you, son.
Mashallah.
May you live long, son.
You must have news to come without
informing us.
Bala, my girl.
You take care of the rest.
With the name of Allah.
Mashallah.
Come on.
May Allah always give them
tasteful fruit.
- Amen.
With the name of Allah.
Pour my girl, pour.
Her hands are shaking, Selcan Hatun.
Our bride is very excited.
May Allah let us see those days...
...we will see yours, too.
-Inshallah.
Inshallah.
-Aygül.
-Mother, wait.
Aygül, welcome. Come, see,
they are boiling.
Mix it, my daughter.
In the evening, we will eat, drink and
have fun. You'll be there, too.
In the evening, we will eat, drink
have fun.
I don't know any feast.
I've never seen such a thing.
I haven't smiled.
Allah had seen my grief.
Allah gave me a baby. Look.
So beautiful. So beautiful.
Like you, mashallah.
You will have one, too.
Allah gave me one, he will give you, too.
Babies are beautiful, they are innocent.
You'll see when you are a mother.
Inshallah, Aygül. Inshallah.
Listen, can you pray for me?
Can you say ''Give a baby to Bala Hatun''?
I wiill, I will.
Aygül is alone.
Bala is not.
She has Osman Bey.
Then, take this. I'll pray for you
and you will take care of my baby.
I will, of course, I will. Don't worry.
I'll look after him.
I'll go. I'll pray a lot.
I have much to do. I'll come to
feast at the evening.
You know what we lack, my Allah.
Help us.
Make us full, my Allah.
So, does Sofia want to be our ally now?
It is what she told me, my Bey.
The Emperor hanged the Monks.
Now they are after Sofia.
Alişar bey died and she has nowhere to go.
She knows that I won't stop before killing
her.
There is something behind it.
Osman, there is blood, revenge, and hate.
What alliance? I kill that snake at
first chance.
She only intends to gain time, Bamsı Bey.
To gain time.
Then we will play her game.
Sıddık!
Go and tell her. I accept her requests.
But I have my terms.
She said that she will accept anything.
Now listen to me carefully. I have three
conditions.
First, she will announce everyone that
Kulucahisar Castle is owned by Osman Bey.
Second, she will come here by herself
and surrender to us.
May Allah bless you.
May Allah bless you, Osman.
Mashallah.
You said three conditions, brother.
What is the third one?
Solidarity is for Allah only.
Konur needs a wife.
She will convert to Islam and swear to
be Konur's wife.
Yes, my Bey. I'd like to join the feast,
my Bey.
But the mission calls. If you allow me,
I should return.
Thank you.
If you allow me, tomorrow I'll visit
my brother Aybar's grave.
Father.
I'll tell him to not concern about you.
As soon as the mission ends, I'll be with you.
Just to finish your mission, I will crush
that castle to ground...
...by my bare fist against the stone
walls.
Come on, come on. Be on your way, son.
- My Bey.
- Yes, Saltuk.
Hazal Hatun wishes to see you. She has
some things to say.
She waits you at Kozalak Hill.
My Bey, a healer came for Aygül Hatun.
Let him come.
Dündar Bey awaits you.
- Welcome, Efendi.
- Thank you, my Bey.
Gündüz Bey spread the word.
I came as soon as I heard.
My daughter is sick. Inshallah her health
will first come from Allah and then by you.
Inshallah, my Bey.
See about it. I'll be back.
Do what is necessary.
Help my daughter, Efendi.
Cerkutay.
Balgay has a new order for you.
What is his order, Kongar?
You came to stop me from killing Osman,
didn't you?
After now, Balgay will not turn any Turk
against his own kind.
I will kill him with my own hands.
Wait, Aygül. Wait, my girl.
Follow this with your eyes, my daughter.
Watch it.
Come on.
I fell.
I used to fall a lot. My brother used to
help me get up.
- Where is her brother?
- We lost him.
Alas...
What do you say, physician?
Isn't there any hope?
With Allah, there is always hope, but...
...she is badly shaken.
She will get better, don't worry.
Not only for her, I've brought a medicine
to relieve your heart.
Your daughter's heal is in this bottle.
- I don't ask anything for that.
- May Allah bless you.
But the important matter we need to talk
about is something else.
Kongar...
My business with Osman didn't
come to an end yet, Kongar.
You will be the fruit of treason...
...and I will be the poison.
You aren't strong enough to kill
Osman Bey.
Craven.
We won't kill Osman...
...you will.
Who are you?
Who do you serve?
Who I am is irrelevant.
What's important is your daughter.
And thorns that rise up in spring.
Don't you think it's time to get rid
of the thorns?
I'll regularly prepare your daughter's
medicine.
About who do I serve...
...both the health of your daughter and
the revenge you will take...
...is a gift from Princess Sofia.
Sofia?
Before it is killed, put the powder
in goat's forage.
The poison will penetrate the animal's
blood and meat.
But it won't kill immediately. The ones who
eat its meat will die naturally.
They will sacrifice the goat and you will
sacrifice them.
This night, both your heart will be
cooled and Dündar Bey will get to be the Bey.
Hear my voice!
One holy migration comes from the steppes.
It is hard to carry for a dead.
A soldier goes first,
an old man comes last.
Move aside, a goat comes on shoulders!
Come on, Bamsı Bey! Shoot that arrow
and let us see who is the fastest in the Tent.
Did you hear that, Konur?
My uncle is talking about me.
I heard it. Try not to choke
on the dust while coming after me.
Come on.
Come one, then, valiants!
With the name of Allah.
Come on, heroes! Come on!
With the name of Allah!
Ya Allah!
Mashallah!
Go on, heroes!
- Go on, heroes!
- Come on!
Come on, Osman!
Come on!
Come on, Osman Bey!
Come on, Baran Alp!
Come on!
Come on, Osman!
Come on, Osman Bey!
Mashallah!
Praise be!
But!
The master of this game...
... is Bamsı Bey!
Valiants! Long ago while
I was still young...
... I could carry two rams
on a single shoulder!
Don't talk large like this again!
Brother?
Ayaz?
My Bey...
Praise be, my Bey.
- May your hands be blessed.
- Amen.
Thank you.
Excuse me, Bey.
They're busy with the meeting
in the Tent. I wanted to meet alone.
That's why I informed you.
Your flaws are fine after all
this longing, Hatun.
Help yourself.
How's Bahadır doing?
My Bahadır is distressed
and thoughtful.
All eyes are on him.
His spirit is uncomfortable.
He's upset about his father the most.
I'm quite good at upsetting
my loved ones.
What happened to you, Dündar Bey?
I thought many mountains would collapse
but my Bey wouldn't. What happened?
Süleyman Şah's son has
lost his way, Hatun.
The mistakes he made in this road
have cost him his children.
Everything that coward Alişar touched
has corroded your heart.
But you must think about your Tent
even if your heart is on fire, Dündar Bey!
You must think about your daughter Aygül!
My Aygül...
Don't do this to yourself, Dündar Bey.
I lost everything I own...
... one by one.
First you,
the Sultan of my heart...
... and then my children.
Doesn't matter if my heart is on
the opposite side of the world...
... my heart is with you.
It's yours.
Don't you know that, Dündar Bey?
You never lost me.
- Did you complete your duty?
- I did, Princess.
I gave the poison for the lamb
to Zöhre Hatun.
What if she gets scared?
What if she refuses to do it?
She'll do it!
She gave everything up so that
her Husband became a Bey.
She'll do it so her husband becomes
the Bey and they don't get exiled.
I don't have a single doubt.
I'll be near the Tent all night so I can
tell you how every one of them died.
I'll never forget what you've done, Aleks.
You'll get your reward.
You're the last thing left
from Master Yannis.
We'll share your pain
and revenge.
I'll take Master Yannis' revenge tonight.
The Kayı Tent...
... will be a huge graveyard.
I'm in a dark place, Hatun.
A deserted, cold,
brutal place.
But you heated my heart like a sun.
I've missed you so much.
Does falling down suit
the mighty Dündar Bey?
Does being dispersed suit him?
Please tell me.
Where's the Bey of
the world I left?
No. this is not my Dündar Bey.
Don't think I removed you
from my heart because...
... you exiled our son, my Bahadır
from the Tent and I followed my son.
The name Dündar is engraved
to my head and my heart.
I've come for my son...
But give the order and I'll stay for you.
Oh, Hazal!
Do I deserve a Hatun with
a mighty heart like you?
You're my man.
It will stay this way until
my last breath.
Bring it, come on.
Let's see.
Wait, make way.
Wonderful!
Good! Mark these.
They're healthy.
Being this one too.
Spare these for the Bey's table, okay?
May it be easy.
Yes, mark them.
Mark them.
They'll kill the goats,
and you'll kill them.
Tonight, your heart will cool down...
... and also Dündar Bey
will take the lead again.
Yes, eat it.
Until you have enough.
So that Osman can have
enough of his death.
Everyone around him...
... everyone who eats from his table...
... shall die one by one.
Eat it.
Praise be!
Prasie be!
People!
We've made a feast!
Many cauldrons are full!
My Osman Bey became a groom,
the fire in his heart has burst!
He came all the way to the bride's house!
Let your bride come and be our crown!
Let her come and honour our Osman Bey!
How wonderful!
Praise be my valiant!
Your hands shall be dexterous,
you shall make more from less.
May your hands, face, words
be sweet like honey.
You shall always smile at your Bey.
May plentifulness always be in your home.
You shall always be grateful.
In the name of Allah!
What did my Osman Bey do?
He laid the table for a wedding feast!
Come on!
What did he do for Bala Hatun?
He sacrificed many, many animals!
Let's go!
Did he break hearts?
Did he say bad words?
He neither broke hearts
nor said bad words!
He lost his heart to his Hatun!
Then Allah shall make them happy!
- Amen!
- May their marriage last long!
Come on!
Come on.
Everyone is here.
Aren't they cooked already?
Whoops.
Brothers! Bring those meats.
- Ayaz Alp is hungry.
- Or Ayaz Alp will eat us all!
Bamsı Bey! They're making fun of me!
In the name of Allah!
My valiants!
Nine types of foods are
eaten at ceremonies.
Red deers, lambs, birds...
And if your Alp friend is with you,
you'd eat a rock for bread!
Bamsı Bey is on fire!
The ground cracks but
the Bey's commands keep coming...
... the sweats are wiped
but the work doesn't end...
... a feast is given
but the food doesn't end.
As long as you're with a friend,
poison is honey for you!
We shall give food to the poor,
a blanket to the cold!
From now on, we shall burn
with the love of holy war!
This is a feast! Eat as you like!
But...
... but commemorate
the Prophet Mohammad!
Now...
Let the tents be tents and let
their lineage grow.
Let the feast begin.
Come on. Where is our poet? He...
He understands us...
He is famous for
his qopuz. (a Turkish instrument)
Hey...
This is the feast of Osman Bey!
Hey! Mashaallah!
Thank you, Bamsı Bey.
Long live my Bey!
- Long live!
- Thanks, Bamsı Bey...
Thanks. Mashaallah.
My father...
See...
Your grandchild Osman grew up and...
...married.
He started a family.
I'm old, father.
I wanted to be a son worthy of you...
I tried during my whole life.
But I couldn't.
But I was unaware, father.
It seems that I was blind...
...and deaf.
Ah...
I'm old like you.
However, I couldn't grow up like you.
I even betrayed my own life.
I betrayed myself and you...
...and your tent.
Forgive me.
I wish you were here...
My mother...
My father...
My Batur..
I wish you were with me.
I wish you hugged me.
You'd be a remedy to my wrongs and...
...my heart.
I wish I didn't do any of these.
I wish we were together...
...in this tent.
The poet always says the truth.
From now on, neither our azans
nor our poets...
...will ever shut.
Bard! (poet)
Horse's foot is like crowbar and bard's
mouth is strong.
- Strike the dombra's cord! ( a Turkish instrument)
- Thanks.
When he became twenty...
He dreamt something holy...
He is the nightmare...
...of the bad people, Osman Bey!
He is so strong...
...down with unbelievers!
Ertuğrul Ghazi's valiant...
Osman Bey is valiant...
He is from an ancient family...
The sky refers to him...
He punished the cruels.
Like a dark wolf, Osman Bey.
With strong weapons...
And hard equipments...
...with valiant Alps...
Osman Bey wrote history.
While the oppressed people
are suffering...
The earth calls for you...
A state has been founded...
Like sky, like Osman Bey.
He became a nightmare for devils...
The sky calls for him...
He punished the cruels...
Like a dark wolf, Osman Bey.
Mashaallah!
Thanks.
My Sheikh...
You brought good to our table.
Pray for us, Inshallah.
Don't leave us without your prayers.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
(In the name of Allah, Most Gracious, Most Merciful)
Thank Allah for creating us as a Muslim.
Amin.
My Allah...
You're our intention and wish.
- Don't let people insult us.
- Amin.
- Keep our effort and love alive.
My Allah...
Our matter is the land...
...and our fight is for Islam.
Make our lands lively...
- and make our people happy.
- Amin.
My Allah...
...make our valiant soldiers'
hearts open...
- and good.
- Amin.
Fulfill their hears with
belief and sacrament.
Amin.
Adorn their life with holy wars..
...make their death with Shahada.
Amin.
My Allah...
Don't make our valiant soldiers'...
- life hard.
- Amin.
Make us stand against cruel...
...and make us merciful towards
good people.
Make us so fair that...
- we can be reliable.
- Amin.
Make us so kind that...
- we can be home to good people.
- Amin.
Make us so erudite that...
- we can be the mind of believers.
- Amin.
Make us so big that...
- we can be the nightmares of bad people.
- Amin.
Al Fatihah.
Daughter.
The feast has begun, father.
Yes, it has.
Osman Bey is doing what he wants.
Let's go.
Okay, daughter. Let's go.
The feast has begun.
They're waiting for us.
Come on, daughter.
Come on.
Uncle...
Welcome.
Thanks.
My uncle...
...is my guest tonight.
In this feast...
...we unite.
Amin.
Dündar Bey...
Here you go.
My Osman Bey is so respectful.
Although his uncle has done bad, he
is good to him.
It's not easy to be Osman Bey.
Your heart must be wide like...
...your anger.
The meal is coming.
Yes...
What's it, Zöhre? You're anxious.
No, I'm not.
Why are you saying that?
Enjoy your meal.
Come on.
Mother, what did you do?
Come on, let's clean it.
Come on.
Dündar Bey...
...it's dark.
Come with us.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
Stop!
Don't...
eat...
...the food!
What happened?
This traitor...
...poisoned the food.
What?
What are you saying?
She's lying.
If you say so...
...eat it then.
If someone is trying to
kill us, I kill that person.
What are you doing, Hazal Hatun?
We didn't even ask her!
Hazal Hatun doesn't do anything
without proof, Gündüz Bey.
- What are you doing?!
- Your lifes...
are my wedding gift for you, Osman.
Now...
If you want to taste
the food, you can do it!
If you don't want to see how you die...
then don't.
There are lots of Beys here!
Why don't you tell us?
I do my job myself, Osman.
From now on, all of you owe me a life.